Guide to the Stanford University, Registrar's Office, records SC1288
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, 1891-1999; Series 6 (Accession ARCH-2013-027)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Carlsen, Catherine - Christy, Valerie, Dec-91; 15 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Chritton, Philip - Crow, Patrick Charles, Dec-91; 16 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Crowe, Ann - Doersch, Todd Dayton, Dec-91; 17 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Doganis, Kyriakos - Ezra, Ann, Dec-91; 18 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Fabela, Angie K. - Fylstra, Mary Beth, Dec-91; 19 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Gabaldon R. Juan Jose - Goodwin, Susan, Dec-91; 20 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Goon, George - Gyori, Philip John, Dec-91; 21 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Ha, Chung Nim - Hegge, Osama H., Dec-91; 22 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Heggem, Richard A. - Howell, Timothy, Dec-91; 23 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Howenstein, Amy - Johnson, William W., Dec-91; 24 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Johnston, Barbara - Kishimoto, Yoriko, Dec-91; 25 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Kishiyama, Jeffrey - Lee, Lynton, Dec-91; 26 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Lee, Man Kwok - Lyzwanski, Ludwik S., Mar-92; 27 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports 1970-1989: Ma, Barry - McWhitnney, Mark, Mar-92; 28 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Marquez, Laura - Mytkowicz, Robert John, Mar-92; 29 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Naas, Robert - Ow, Miranda J., Mar-92; 30 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Paal, Adam F. - Qzqa, Teresa F., Mar-92; 31 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Raab, Frank E. - Rzchowski, Mark S., Mar-92; 32 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Sa, Cynthia Claire - Shyy, Bor Wen, Mar-92; 33 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Si, Yiu-Pong, Patrick - Stevenson, Shelly Hollice, Mar-92; 34 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Steward, David L. - Tomer, Janice, Mar-92; 35 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Tomic, Francisco E. - Vuong, Truc Minh, Mar-92; 36 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Wacha, Jason - Wilkis, Robert M., Mar-92; 37 (Box 2)
  - Grade Report 1970-1989: Willard, Andrew R. - Zytko, Mark J., Mar-92; 38 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Forms Pre-Decentralization (87-90) Abbot, Jonathan - Zabora, Kim, Jun-92; X1 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Program Authorizaton Petitions (95-96) Aalami, Florian - Zoumos, George, X1 (Box 2)
  - Coterm Applications: Accetta, A. - Zeledon R., X1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Aaberg, Lynn - Byun, Kuk Whan, May-93; 1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Caballer, Carlos - Dyson, Rebecca L., May-93; 2 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Eades, Rebecca J. - Gyugyi, Paul J., May-93; 3 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Ha, Albert - Juvel, Philippe, May-93; 4 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Kabakain, Adour - Lyvers, Raissa T., May-93; 5 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Ma, Albert - Monzon, Patricia, May-93; 6 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Monica, Katherine A. - Qureshy, Nafees, May-93; 7 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Raab, Gregory E. - Szwed, Michael, May-93; 8 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards: Taam, Gregory - Zylbert, Barbara, May-93; 9 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: Aalami, Florian B. - Grayson, Saldah (93-97), Jan-98; #001 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: Greves, Denise D. - Namphy, Paul C. (93-97), Jan-98; #002 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: Nabae, Hitomi - Wazhullam, Nahhud (93-97), Jan-98; #003 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: Weatherspoon, Darryl - Zynger, Debra L. (93-97), Jan-98; #004 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: AA - KW, Dec-99; #001 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Card: LA - ZW, Dec-99; #002 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Cards 1999-2000: AAB - Zynger, Apr-03; 1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Cards 2000-2001: Aarabi - Zussman, Apr-03; 1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Change Cards 1999-2003: Aaron - Zweig, Jan-06; 1 (Box 2)
  - Add/Drop Cards 1999-2004: Abadi - Zwick, Jan-06; 1 (Box 2)
  - Problem Cards: Abbruzzese - Zussman, Jan-06; 1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Autumn 1968/69 - Winter 1977/78, 1 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Autumn 1978/79 - Winter 1981/82, 2 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Spring 1981/82 - Spring 1984/85, 3 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Autumn 1985/86 - Autumn 1988/89, 4 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Autumn 1989/90 - Autumn 1992/93, 5 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution Reports: Winter 1992/93 - Spring 1993/94, 6 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Nov-75; 28 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 67/68 (Psyc, MINE), 28 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 67/68 (HIN, CoEd, AA, ALJ, BioL, Hum, Math, Pols), 28 (Box 3)
  - 1915 Reports, 28 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Nov-75; 29 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 67/68 (Math, Pols, Psys), 29 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 67/68 (ME, EES, ELG, SRC), 29 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Nov-75; 30 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 67/68 (ELP, SPEC, CE, Hum, Math, Psys, Micr), 30 (Box 3)
  - 1870 Reports, 30 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 26-Nov-75; 31 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 67/68 (Psys, Micr), 31 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 67/68 (HIN, Comm, Econ), 31 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. (Lib, Che, CE, ALJ, BioL, Hum, Econ), 31 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 26-Nov-75; 32 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 68/69 (BioL, Hum, Econ, Math, Pols, Psyc, PETE), 32 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 68/69 (EE, Comm, Cla), 32 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 26-Nov-75; 33 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 68/69 (Comm, CLG, Econ, ELG, Stat), 33 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 68/69 (ME, Educ, Math), 33 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 26-Nov-75; 34 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 68/69 (ME, Educ, Stat, EES, CE,APPH), 34 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 1-Dec-75; 35 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 68/69 (EE, CLC, Ant, Comm, Hum, Math, Pols, Psyc, Econ), 35 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 1-Dec-75; 36 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 68/69 (Engl), 36 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 69/70 (CH E, CE, BioL, Hum, Math, Pols, Mus), 36 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 2-Dec-75; 37 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 69/70 (Math, Pols, Mus, Psych), 37 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 69/70 (CH E. CE, BioL, RLGN, Engl), 37 (Box 3)
  - 1920 Reports, 37 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 2-Dec-75; 38 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 69/70 (BioL, RLGN, Math, Psys, SRC), 38 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 69/70 (LLAB, OPR, AIRS, Germ, Arch), 38 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 3-Dec-75; 39 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 69/70 (AIRS, Germ, Arch, Slav, LLAB, Ch E, CE, RLGN, ECON), 39 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 3-Dec-75; 40 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 69/70 (RLGN, ECON, Math, Psyc), 40 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 69/70 (LLAB, Hist, OBGY), 40 (Box 3)
  - 1828 Reports, 40 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 5-Dec-75; 41 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 69/70 (Path, Medicine), 41 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 70/71 (Ch E., CE, RLGN, Mat, Pols, Phil), 41 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 16-Dec-75; 42 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 70/71 (Math, Phil), 42 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 70/71 (Engr, Chem, CL H, Math, Econ), 42 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Dec-75; 44 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 70/71 (LLAB, EE, Germ, SCTR, Engr, Chem, Anth), 44 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Dec-75; 45 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 70/71 (Engr, Chem, Anth, Math, FRA, Soc), 45 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 70/71 (Comm, BioL), 45 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Dec-75; 46 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 70/71 (Comm, BioL, Econ), 46 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 71/72 (EE, AM, Comm, ITAL, Math), 46 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 19-Dec-75; 47 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 71/72 (Comm, Ital, Math, Germ, Dram, Stat), 47 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 71/72 (Lib, AM, Engr, BioL, Germ), 47 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 20-Dec-75; 49 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 71/72 (Soc, SP, 49 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 71/72 (Lib, CE, EE, Engl, Hist, Phsc, Phys, AA, Educ), 49 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Dec-75; 50 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 71/72 (Lib, AA, Educ, Ch E, Anth, Arch, Econ, Engl, Port, Ling, CS, Psych), 50 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Dec-75; 51 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 71/72 (Ling, CS, Psyc, AFR), 51 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 71/72 (LLAB, Hist, Hum, SCTR), 51 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 72/73 (Lib, AA, PE), 51 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 23-Dec-75; 52 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 72/73 (Lib, AA, PE, HOCH, Engl, Rlgn, Chem, Hum, MUS, Phil, Dram, Pysc), 52 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 29-Dec-75; 53 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 72/73 (Phil, Dram, Psyc, Stat, TRS), 53 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 72/73 (Lib, Ch E, CE, Span, Soc, BioL, Fren), 53 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 29-Dec-75; 54 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 72/73 (Soc, BioL, Fren, Chem, L Am, Hist, Ling, Mus, Psyc), 54 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 31-Dec-75; 55 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 72/73 (Mus, Psyc, SSCI, Spa, Geol, TRS), 55 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 72/73 (LLAB, CE, EE, Chem, CLH, Ling, Engl), 55 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 31-Dec-75; 56 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 72/73 (CLH, Ling, Engl, Mus, Geol, GPH, SWOP, Lib, PE, AA, EES, OPR, Chem, Anth), 56 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 2-Jan-76; 57 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 72/73 (OPR, Chem, Ant, CLH, Hist, Hum, Mus, Phil, Dram, Stat, TRS, Law), 57 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 2-Jan-76; 58 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 72/73 (Stat, TRS, Law), 58 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 72/73 (LLAB, OCI, AAPH, Rlgn, Math, VTS, LIB, CE, EDUC), 58 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 9-Jan-75; 59 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 73/74 (Lib, CE, Educ, EE, Arch, Art, Econ, Engl, Math), 59 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Jan-75; 60 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 73/74 (FR A, Phsc, Phys, CS, AFR, SLE, Lib, CE, PE), 60 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Jan-75; 61 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 73/74 (Lib, CE, PE, EE, Anth, Arch, Econ, Engl, Math), 61 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 1-Mar-76; 61B (Box 3)
  - Rerunning of Box 61A, 61B (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 9-Feb-76; 62 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 73/74 (Engl, Math, FR A, Phsc, Phys, Dram, Stat, SLE), 62 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 73/74 (Lib, AA, PE), 62 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 9-Feb-76; 63 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 73/74 (Lib, AA, PE, Ch E, Biol, Ital, GE A, Phyc, SSCI, TRS, Lib, Che E, PE), 63 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 10-Feb-76; 64 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 73/74 (Lib, Ch E, PE, CE, AL C, APPH, Comm, Econ, Fren, Ital, Pols, Mus), 64 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 10-Feb-76; 65 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 73/74 (ITAL, Pols, Mus, Psyc, PHRM, PHSL, SLE), 65 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 73/74 (LLAB, EE, AM, Hist), 65 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 11-Feb-76; 66 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 73/74 (Hum, Urbn), 66 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 74/75 (Lib, Educ, PE, AM, ENGR, Hu B, AL C), 66 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 11-Feb-76; 67 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 74/75 (Engr, Hu B, AL, Biol, Econ, Engl, Math, FRA, Phsc, Phys, CS, Phys), 67 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 12-Feb-76; 68 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 74/75 (Phys, CS, Phys, AFR, SLE), 68 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 74/75 (Lib, Educ, PE, AM, EE), 68 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Feb-76; 70 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 74/75 (Germ, Phsc, Ling, Phs, Stat, CS, SLE), 70 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 74/75 (Lib, EE), 70 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Feb-76; 71 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 74/75 (AM, Econ, Engl, Psyc, SSCI, SLE, Lib, EE, PE), 71 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Feb-76; 72 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 74/75 (Lib, EE, PE, EE, Arch, Art, Econ, Engl, Germ, Slav, Phil, Span), 72 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Feb-76; 73 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 74/75 (Slav, Phil, Span, Phsc, Psyc, SSCI, Sp A, Geol, SLE), 73 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 74/75 (LLAB, OPR, OPR, Mus, Biol), 73 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Feb-76; 74 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 74/75 (OPR, Mus, Biol, Phil, VTS), 74 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 12-Jul-77; 75 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 75/76 (007-110, 120-254, 255-380), 75 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 4-Jul-77; 75 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 61/62 (Starting from Psyc), 75 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 12-Jul-77; 76 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 75/76 (Econ - Relg, Math - Mus, Phil - Cut), 76 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Jul-77; 77 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 75/76 (Law-SLE), 77 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 75/76 (Lib-PE, AA-ME), 77 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Jul-77; 78 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 75/76 (EES-HUB, Bidl-Lam, Hist-Ling), 78 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 13-Jul-77; 80 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 75/76 (Mats-Econ, Engl-Astr, Pols-SLE, LLAB-PE), 80 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 14-Jul-77; 81 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 75/76 (AA-OPR, OSV-Biol, Chem-Hist), 81 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 14-Jul-77; 82 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 75/76 (Hum-Mus, Phil-Stat, CS-SLE), 82 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 14-Jul-77; 83 (Box 3)
  - Sum. Qtr. 75/76 (020-210, 251-540, 550-997), 83 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 14-Jul-77; 84 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 76/77 (007-001, 060-493, 091-001, 120-4000, 130-101, 190-301, 200-110, 340-199), 84 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 14-Jul-77; 85 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 76/77 (350-021, 390-199, 390-199, 450-350, 450-350, 540-167), 85 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 15-Jul-77; 86 (Box 3)
  - Aut. Qtr. 76/77 (540-650, 600-999), 86 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 76/77 (007-060, Lib-Educ), 86 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 15-Jul-77; 87 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 76/77 (PE-EE, Engr-Anth, Art-Comm), 87 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 15-Jul-77; 88 (Box 3)
  - Win. Qtr. 76/77 (Econ-Rlgn, Mst-Port, Ling-Pols), 88 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 29-Feb-80; 90 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 76/77 (020-103), 90 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Jun-80; 91 (Box 3)
  - Spr. Qtr. 76/77 (007-001 - 400-163), 91 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Aug-81; 92 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 76/77 (400.171 -999.093), 92 (Box 3)
  - Sum. 76/77 (020-374, 060-470), 92 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Aug-81; 93 (Box 3)
  - Sum. 76/77 (060-480, 995-123), 93 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 77/78 (007-001, 120-299), 93 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 94 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 77/78 (120-300 to 512-299), 94 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 95 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 77/78 (522-001, 999-091), 95 (Box 3)
  - Win. 77/78 (007-001, 060-496), 95 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 96 (Box 3)
  - Win. 77/78 (091-001, 400-001), 96 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 97 (Box 3)
  - Win. 77/78 (400-002, 920-400), 97 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 98 (Box 3)
  - Win. 77/78 (990-131, 999-092), 98 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 77/78 (007-001, 700-336), 98 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 99 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 77/78 (700-390, 997-199), 99 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 77/78 (005-815, 378-260), 99 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 100 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 77/78 (380-001, 980-360), 100 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-82; 101 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 77/78 (990-001, 999-093), 101 (Box 3)
  - Sum. 77/78 (020-379, 995-122), 101 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Aug-82; 102 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 78/79 (Dept. 007 - Dept. 450-019), 102 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 16-Jan-82; 103 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 78/79 (450-044, 999-091), 103 (Box 3)
  - Win. 78/79 (007-001 to 120-228), 103 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Aug-82; 104 (Box 3)
  - Win. 78/79 (120-229 to 540-174A), 104 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Jun-82; 106 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 78/79 (257-021 to 512-272), 106 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, 2-Sep-81; 107 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 78/79 (Dept. 512-Dept. 050), 107 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-83; 108 (Box 3)
  - Spr. 78/79 (Dept. 60 to Dept. 999, Dept. 20 to Dept. 997), 108 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Mar-83; 109 (Box 3)
  - Sum. 78/79 (Dept. 020 to Dept. 833), 109 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Nov-84; 109 (Box 3)
  - Sum. 78/79 (833 to 995, 060 to 020), 109 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 79/80 (Dept. 007 to Dept. 340), 109 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Nov-84; 110 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 79/80 (340 to 610), 110 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Nov-84; 111 (Box 3)
  - Aut. 79/80 (620 to 999), 111 (Box 3)
  - Win. 79/80 (007-130), 111 (Box 3)
  - End Quarter Reports, Nov-84; 112 (Box 3)
  - Win. 79/80 (130 to 450), 112 (Box 3)
  - 1. Aut. Qtr. Reports (English-Mil. Sci), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Mining - Speech), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Engineering), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. Qtr. Reports (English - Mil. Science), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Qtr. Reports (Mining - Speech), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 6. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Biology 300 J), 1946-1947; 59 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Biology 300N - Journ.), 1946-1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (English - Journ.), 1946-1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Engineering), 1946-1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Law - Phys. Sci.), 1946-1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Physics - Speech), 1946-1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 6. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Engineering), 1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 7. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Engineering - Humanities 200), 1947; 60 (Box 4)
  - 1. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Humanities 235 - Speech), 1947; 61 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Education), 1947-1948; 61 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Engr. - Mil. Sci.), 1947-1948; 61 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Min. Sci. - Speech), 1947-1948; 61 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Education), 1947-1948; 61 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. Qtr. Reports (Engr. - English 2A), 1947-1948; 61 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Qtr. Reports (Eng. 2A - Mil. Sci.), 1947-1948; 62 (Box 4)
  - 2. Win. Qtr. Reports (Min. Sci. - Speech), 1947-1948; 62 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Econ.), 1947-1948; 62 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Engr.), 1947-1948; 62 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Engl. - Library), 1947-1948; 62 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. Qtr. Reports, 1947-1948; 63 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Math. - Phys. Therapy), 1947-1948; 63 (Box 4)
  - 3. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Food Research), 1948; 63 (Box 4)
  - 4. Sum. Qtr. Reports (German-Speech), 1948; 63 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ.), 1948-1949; 63 (Box 4)
  - 6. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Engr. - Mech. Engr.), 1948-1949; 63 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Mech. Engr. 118 - Law), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Math. - Physiology), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Pol. Sci. - Statistics), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ.), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Qtr. Reports (Educ. Hyg. - German), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Phys. Ther.), 1948-1949; 64 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Qtr. Reports (Phsycis - Statistics), 1948-1949; 65 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Econ.), 1948-1949; 65 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (English - Law), 1948-1949; 65 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Engr.), 1948-1949; 65 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Math. - Physics 28), 1948-1949; 65 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Physics 29 - Physiol), 1948-1949; 66 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Soc. Sci. - Statistics), 1948-1949; 66 (Box 4)
  - 3. Summer Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Food Research), 1948-1949; 66 (Box 4)
  - 4. Summer Qtr. Reports (German - Speech), 1948-1949; 66 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ.), 1949-1950; 66 (Box 4)
  - 6. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Educ. Hyg. - Hist), 1949-1950; 66 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hoover Inst. - Phys. Ed.), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Phys. Sci. - Statistics), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ.), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. Qtr. Reports (Engr. - German), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Phys. Ther.), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. Qtr. Reports (Physics - Speech 350), 1949-1950; 67 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Qtr. Reports (Speech 294 - Statistics), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Econ.), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Engr.), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Engl. - Law), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Library-Physiol), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 6. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Pol. Sci. - Statistics), 1949-1950; 68 (Box 4)
  - 1. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Food Research), 1949-1950; 69 (Box 4)
  - 2. Sum. Qtr. Reports (German - Speech), 1949-1950; 69 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Air Sci. - Education), 1950-1951; 69 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (ED. Hyg. - History), 1950-1951; 69 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hoov. Inst. - Phys. Ed.), 1950-1951; 69 (Box 4)
  - 6. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Phys. Ed. - Sociol. 136), 1950-1951; 69 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Sociol. 147 - Statistics), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 2. Win. Qtr. Reports (Air. Sci. - Education), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. Qtr. Reports (Educ. Hyg. - Hoov. Inst.), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. Qtr. Reports (Humanities - Physics), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Qtr. Reports (Physiol - Statistics), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 6. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Air Sci. - Econ.), 1950-1951; 70 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Mech. Engr.), 1950-1951; 71 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. Qtr. Reports (English - Library), 1950-1951; 71 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Math - Physiol.), 1950-1951; 71 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Pol. Sci. - Statistics), 1950-1951; 71 (Box 4)
  - 5. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Engl. 395), 1950-1951; 71 (Box 4)
  - 1. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Food Res. - Geog. 208), 1951; 72 (Box 4)
  - 2. Sum. Qtr. Reports (German - Speech), 1951; 72 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Qtr. Reports (Air Science), 1951-1952; 73 (Box 4)
  - 2. Mil. Sci.15 (Mineral Sci. G 185), 73 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Qtr. Reports (Min. Sci. G 190 - Stat. 110), 1951-1952; 74 (Box 4)
  - 2. Win. Qtr. Reports (Stat-Ed), 1951-1952; 74 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Educ. - Hist. 12), 1951-1952; 74 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. Qtr. Reports (Hist. 12- PE 21), 1951-1952; 74 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Qtr. Reports (PE 121 - Psych 280), 1951-1952; 74 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. L.S2 - Sum Hist. 10, 1951-1952; 75 (Box 4)
  - 2. Sum. Hist.10 - Aut. Classics, 1952-1953; 75 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (Classics - Hist.), 1952-1953; 75 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. (Hist. - Psych), 1952-1953; 75 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. (Psych - Educ), 1952-1953; 75 (Box 4)
  - 6. ends Aut. E.E, 1952-1953; 75 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. (M.E. - Sp Dr.), 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Sp, 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. (Air. Sci - Cl), 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. (Cl - Math), 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. Math - Spr. FRI, 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 6. ends Spr. Educ., 1952-1953; 76 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. (Educ. - Econ), 1952-1953; 77 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Econ - Hist), 1952-1953; 77 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (Hist. - Sp., 1952-1953; 77 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (Sp., 1952-1953; 77 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Econ. - Aut. Men PE, 1952-1953; 77 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. (PE - Eng), 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Eng. - Phys.), 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. Phys. - Win. Ed., 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. (Educ. - Geol.), 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. (G, 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. (S. Sc. - Sp. Dr.), 1953-1954; 78 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Sp, 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Educ. - Econ.), 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (Econ. - Hist.), 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (Hist. - Psych.), 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Psych. - Sum. Ed., 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 6. Sum. (Educ. - Biol.), 1953-1954; 79 (Box 4)
  - 1. Sum. Biol. - Aut. Educ., 1953-1954; 80 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Educ. - G, 1954-1955; 80 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (G&RL - Anth), 1954-1955; 80 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. Antho - Win. Ph. Th., 1954-1955; 80 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. (Aero. - G&R), 1954-1955; 80 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. (G&R - Hum), 1954-1955; 80 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. (Hum), 1954-1955; 81 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Bus), 1954-1955; 81 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (EE), 1954-1955; 81 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (English), 1954-1955; 81 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. (Math - Anat), 1954-1955; 81 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. (Bact), 1954-1955; 82 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Music), 1954-1955; 82 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (EE), 1955-1956; 82 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. (G&R), 1955-1956; 82 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. Min. Sci - Spr. M.E., 1955-1956; 82 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. (Arch.), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Hist.), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (Biol.), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (Hist.), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. (Min. Sc.), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 6. Spr. (Educ), 1955-1956; 83 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. (EE), 1955-1956; 84 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Sp & Dr.), 1955-1956; 84 (Box 4)
  - 3. Sum. (Music - Law), 1955-1956; 84 (Box 4)
  - 1. End of '55-56 Reports - Spr. (M.E. Lab - Arch) Aut. 56 (Air - Art), 1955-1956; 95 (Box 4)